class Database {
  static List<Map<String, dynamic>> data = [
    {
      "question":
          "1.Who developed the Flutter Framework and continues to maintain it today?",
      "options": ["Facebook", "Google", "Oracle", "Microsoft"],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "2.Which widget is used for creating a scrollable list of items in Flutter?",
      "options": ["TextWidget", "ListView", "GridWidget", "Container"],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "3.What is the purpose of the 'pubspec.yaml' file in a Flutter project?",
      "options": [
        "It defines the project's app icon.",
        "It specifies the project's dependencies.",
        "It controls the project's layout and design.",
        "It manages user authentication."
      ],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "4.Which Flutter command is used to run the app on an Android emulator or device?",
      "options": [
        "flutter install",
        "flutter build",
        "flutter run",
        "flutter debug"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "5.What is the primary function of the MaterialApp widget in a Flutter app?",
      "options": [
        "Define the app's theme and layout.",
        "Create a new instance of the app.",
        "Handle user authentication.",
        "Manage state in the app."
      ],
      "answer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "6.Which widget is used to display a modal bottom sheet in Flutter?",
      "options": [
        "AlertDialog",
        "BottomNavigationBar",
        "BottomSheet",
        "Scaffold"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question": "7.In Flutter, what does the term 'widget' refer to?",
      "options": [
        "A user's profile picture",
        "A small graphical component that can be combined to build the UI",
        "A unit of data storage",
        "A built-in Flutter app template"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":
          "8.Which package is commonly used for handling HTTP requests in Flutter?",
      "options": ["http_requests", "network_io", "http_client", "http"],
      "answer": 3,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "9.What is the primary purpose of the StatefulWidget class in Flutter?",
      "options": [
        "To create a stateless widget",
        "To store mutable state data that can change over time",
        "To define the app's theme",
        "To handle user authentication"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":
          "10.Which widget is used for creating a tabbed navigation interface in Flutter?",
      "options": ["TabView", "TabBar", "TabLayout", "TabNavigator"],
      "answer": 1,
    },
  ];
}
